Brooke Perlee

Product Manager

Personal Info

Address

10 New Street Boston, MA 02128

Phone

+1(631)764-6759

E-mail

brooke.perlee214@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/b-perlee/

Skills

CRM Software

Experienced SalesForce admin

Creating Tutorials

Skilled with Camtasia and Adobe Captivate to create tutorials

Communication Skills

Presented product software at varying levels of technicality

UI/UX Experience

Proficient with Sketch design and InVision prototyping

German

Learned basic German to improve communication with HQ

Health IT Skills

HITECH Compliance

DICOM Conformance

HL7 Integration

FDA Standards

Agile Methodology

Evidence-Based Practice

Data Analysis

Clinical Healthcare Experience

Healthcare Product Manager, experienced with diagnostic imaging devices that integrate hardware and software. Launched a software upgrade that generated \$1.08 million in direct orders within the first two months of availability, and \$4.77 million in associated hardware orders. Adaptable and detail-oriented, with a unique clinical perspective gained from clinical experience and Health IT background. Committed to provide the healthcare community with solutions that can make a meaningful difference in improving quality of care, better clinical outcomes and an enhanced patient experience.

Experience

Jan 2017 present

Product Manager

Heidelberg Engineering, Inc.

Promotion to Product Manager (10/2018 - Present)

Associate Product Manager (01/2017 - 10/2018)

Responsibilities

- Product owner of hardware and software elements of the US Spectralis product line
- Interfaces with HQ product management and engineering teams to incorporate US
 VOC feedback in feature design and usability improvements
- Facilitates research initiatives and when applicable collaborates to translate research initiatives to clinical utility
- Represents HEI at trade shows and scientific conferences to present products, monitor market activity, and stay current on clinical and technological trends
- Analyzes competitive products and incorporates industry strategy into product roadmap
- Develops training materials for sales, clinical applications trainers, field service engineers and the customer care team for strategic product launch and continued product success
- Defines key success metrics for product launches and post-launch to drive continuous product improvements

Achievements

- Managed an FDA field correction for a software feature that impacted 300+ systems
- Reduced the number of open customer support cases per month by 51.4% through SalesForce data analysis and subsequent process redesign
- Launched multiple products with differing technical specifications and clinical utility simultaneously

Dec 2015 -Jan 2017

Clinical Applications Support Specialist

Heidelberg Engineering, Inc.

Responsibilities

- Provided expert clinical knowledge and product support for HEI devices to clinicians and operators via phone, online support, and in person
- Performed issue identification, escalation and resolution for networking, software, hardware and user related issues

Achievements

- Created customer focused training materials using Adobe Captivate and Camtasia
- Proposed, launched and maintained a social media strategy
- Assumed responsibilities of managing product lines in absence of product manager

Sep 2015 - **Se**

Senior Ophthalmic Technician

Ophthalmic Surgical Assistant

Dec 2015

Ophthalmic Consultants of Boston

Sep 2015

Jan 2013 -

New England Retina Associates

Education

Apr 2017 Sacred Heart University, Masters of Science

Healthcare Informatics

May 2013 Sacred Heart University, Bachelors of Science

Cellular and Molecular Biology; Minor: Chemistry